[♪♪♪]
SERENA:
Marcus.
How are you?
Ask me in an hour.
[WHISPERING]
I thought I'd try
one last time.
You should have stayed in
San Francisco, Dr Kogan.
[WHISPERING]
By signing this consent form,
you'd be donating your
body to a noble cause.
You'd...
have a second chance,
through my research, to live again.
You know what I did.
My brother and two cops
are dead because of me.
I'm not looking for a second chance.
But I'm not the only one
with a death sentence, am I?
Do you think I'm gonna
cure your cancer, Serena?
I'm not worried about myself.
I'm worried about the
future of the human race.
I'll sell it to you.
For what?
A kiss.
SERENA:
Mm.
MARCUS:
Oh...
So that's what death tastes like.
[SERENA SIGHS]
[DOOR SLAMS]
You're doing something very noble.
MARCUS:
No, I'm guilty.
Just cut me up until there's nothing left.
[♪♪♪]
PRIEST: Yea, though I walk through
the valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil, for thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff, they comfort me.
[MARCUS BREATHING SHARPLY]
[TABLE WHIRRING]
WARDEN:
Do you have any last words?
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[♪♪♪]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
MAN [ON RADIO]:
Vanguard, this is Blackjack 6.
Missile inbound to Skynet target.
TTO 11 seconds. Danger close.
[COMPUTER CHIMING]
[GUNFIRE]
[CHATTERING]
- MAN 1: Move! Move!
- WOMAN: Let's go, let's go! Move it!
MAN 2 [ON RADIO]:
Connor is on the ground.
[EXPLOSIONS]
OLSEN:
This mission is a quick in-and-out.
Command deems the information
on those computers
to be of the highest priority.
[EXHALES]
BARBAROSA [ON RADIO]:
Connor, there's no sign of the machines.
They're gone.
DAVID [ON RADIO]:
It's way too quiet.
BARBAROSA [ON RADIO]:
It's almost like they're waiting for us.
[SOLDIERS BREATHING HEAVILY]
[♪♪♪]
DAVID [ON RADIO]:
What the hell's that smell, man?
Ugh.
JOHN [ON RADIO]:
You seeing this?
Olsen. Objective located.
There's something else you have to see.
[GROANING AND GIBBERING]
MAN 1:
Hard wall.
OLSEN: Get what we came for, Barbarosa.
The clock's ticking.
Spread out, secure the perimeter.
I got a big gap over here.
JOHN:
Why didn't we know about this?
BARBAROSA: Sir, I think this
is what Command's looking for.
I'm in their source code.
These people are being taken
to San Francisco.
Some sort of R and D project
for a new Terminator.
OLSEN:
Send it to Command.
BARBAROSA:
It's uploading. I need two minutes.
Wait, wait, wait. Go back. Go back.
Stop.
[MEN CHATTERING]
- BARBAROSA: T-800.
- DAVID: A new Terminator.
It's like you said it would be.
- It's worse.
- OLSEN: Get your nose out of that.
None of your business.
You're not leading this mission.
All right, let's cut these sorry
bastards loose. Come on. Let's go.
- Jericho, come in.
- MAN 2: Watch that.
OLSEN:
Come in, Jericho.
Connor, get your ass topside.
Remind those men
they need to answer me on the
radio, even if they're dead.
Connor!
[GRUNTING]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING IN DISTANCE]
[PANTING]
OLSEN [ON RADIO]:
Connor, get those men to respond.
JOHN:
Olsen, something's wrong up here.
OLSEN [ON RADIO]:
Topside, come in.
[JET ENGINES FIRING]
JOHN:
Outbound enemy aircraft. I'm in pursuit.
There's human prisoners aboard that thing!
Get after it!
[GASPS]
OLSEN [ON RADIO]:
Data transfer complete.
Connor, we're joining you topsi...
[ALARM BEEPING]
[JOHN GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Olsen.
[RUMBLING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[JOHN SIGHS]
MAN [ON RADIO]:
Bravo 10, Bravo 10, do you copy? Over.
Eagle 1 to Bravo 10.
Bravo 10, do you copy? Over.
Bravo 10, Bravo 10, do you copy? Over?
Here.
MAN [ON RADIO]:
Bravo 10, identify. Over.
[SHOUTS]
Connor.
MAN [ON RADIO]: We'll send units to the extraction
point. How many survivors are on-site? Over.
One.
MAN [ON RADIO]:
Copy.
[♪♪♪]
[THUNDER CRASHING]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[SCREAMING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
PILOT:
Return to base, sir?
- RTB?
- Negative.
- Take me to Command.
- Sir?
Command.
Roger. Rerouting.
[♪♪♪]
PILOT:
Request has been denied.
Command doesn't wanna give up
their position. Radio comms only.
- Are they down there?
- Request has been denied, sir.
Need-to-know only.
That's straight from the top.
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
JOHN:
You open up that ramp
and you tell them I need
divers for a lock-in! Now!
This is crazy.
ASHDOWN:
John Connor.
Prophesized leader of the Resistance.
Soldier, you put every man and
woman in this sub in jeopardy
with your little frogman stunt.
What the hell are you doing here?
- What did we find down there?
- You'll be briefed
- on a need-to-know basis.
- Well, I need to know.
Because my men died down in that hole.
What did we find down there?
We found a solution, Connor,
that can end this war once and for all.
We know the machines use shortwave
transmitters to communicate.
Our intel has located a hidden signal
under the primary channel.
It allows for direct
control of the machines.
Skynet's a machine, and like all machines,
it has an off switch.
Does it work?
Will it work? Yes.
Have we field tested it? No.
Give it to me.
I'll do it.
I'll test it.
Connor and his tech-comm unit
have an excellent record.
ASHDOWN:
All right.
All right. Hmph.
Take Connor topside. Prepare for lockout.
Connor, we do this right, the war is over.
We mount our offensive in four days.
LOSENKO:
Connor.
These are the codes for the signal.
- Good luck.
- Why four days?
A kill list was intercepted from Skynet.
It says everyone in this room
will be dead by week's end.
You're number two on the list.
- Well, who's number one?
- An unknown. A civilian. Kyle Reese.
[♪♪♪]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[CHATTERING]
OLSEN [VOICE-OVER]:
Jericho, come in.
Come in, Jericho.
JOHN:
Barnes.
My brother, he didn't make it, did he?
[♪♪♪]
SARAH [ON TAPE]: This is tape number
28 of Sarah Connor to my son, John.
What's most difficult for
me is trying to decide
what to tell you and what not to.
Should I tell you about your father?
Will it affect your decision
to send him back in time to protect me,
knowing that he is your father?
And he'll be younger than you.
Only a teenager when you meet him.
God, a person could go
crazy thinking about this.
But if you don't send Kyle,
you can never be,
and Skynet will win the war.
[COMPUTER CHIRPING]
KATE:
You want to talk about him?
Kyle is out there somewhere alone,
and Skynet is hunting him.
What about the signal?
What do you think?
- KATE: If it works, it's incredible.
- Yeah.
- We have to be careful.
- I agree.
- But we have to try.
- Okay.
All right, then start with something small,
something we're familiar with.
We should try to capture a
Hydrobot, bring it in for testing.
Yeah.
What is it, John?
Kill Kyle Reese, reset the future,
no John Connor.
[♪♪♪]
[SHOUTING]
Hey!
[CREAKING]
[GRUNTING]
Come with me if you want to live.
[♪♪♪]
What is that?
[SHOTGUN RACKS]
She doesn't talk, but you need to start.
[KYLE PANTS]
Where'd you get that jacket?
- The other guy didn't need it.
- Oh?
You see that red?
It stands for blood.
It's a symbol of the Resistance.
You're obviously not a Resistance
fighter, so take it off.
Take it off!
You point a gun at someone,
you'd better be ready to pull the trigger.
Now, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
- What the hell was that thing?
- Terminator.
T-600.
[♪♪♪]
What day is it?
What year?
2018.
What happened here?
Judgment Day happened.
I gotta get out of here.
You can't go on foot.
The machines will cut you down.
You need speed.
I need a car.
Well, look,
there's some by Griffith Observatory.
- They don't run, though.
- Take me.
[SQUEAKING]
KYLE:
Get down!
[MARCUS COUGHS]
[ALL COUGHING]
KYLE:
That was a Hunter-Killer.
Thanks to you, they know we're here.
What's your name, kid?
Kyle Reese.
Come on.
[WHIRRING AND SQUEALING]
We burned out his transmitter so
it can't talk to any of its pals.
But he can still receive.
Turn it on.
You got it?
MAN 1:
Hold it down, hold it down.
Turn the signal up.
[SIGNAL BEEPING]
[ROBOT POWERING DOWN]
Give me the strap.
- Holy shit.
- Do you believe it?
MAN 2:
All right. Grab it tight.
WOMAN:
The signal has to be continuous.
If there's any interruption...
[GRUNTING]
JOHN [DISTORTED]:
Okay.
Let's rig up a portable shortwave, I need
to test it on something larger in the field.
All right.
Destroy this thing.
[♪♪♪]
MARCUS:
So where are the cars?
KYLE:
You don't wanna go out after dark.
Hunter-Killers have infrared,
hunt better at night.
We'll all go tomorrow morning.
- MARCUS: What is that?
- Two-day-old coyote.
Pah. Better than three-day-old coyote.
KYLE: Hey, hey!
MARCUS: Shh.
[SHOTGUN RACKS]
- Grab it.
- What?
Grab it.
Magic.
[MARCUS SIGHS]
- MARCUS: Got it?
- Yeah.
Thanks.
[♪♪♪]
Does this radio work?
No.
My dad tried to fix it,
but he could never get it to work.
MARCUS:
Hold that.
Where is everybody?
They're gone.
So why are you still here?
Because we're the Resistance, L.A. branch.
Welcome to the headquarters.
Resisting what?
Machines. Skynet.
- Just the two of you?
- Yeah.
How come you're not wearing one of these?
Because I haven't earned mine yet.
I hope he's listening to this.
We've been fighting a long time
and we have all lost so very much,
so many loved ones gone.
But you are not alone.
There are pockets of Resistance
all around the planet.
We are at the brink.
Do you wanna see a magic trick?
Hold that up.
Press the button.
[RADIO STATIC BUZZING]
JOHN [ON RADIO]: Effective range of their
main weapon is less than 100 metres.
They pack a lot of firepower,
but the T-600s are heavy and slow.
They are a primitive design.
- Who is that?
- JOHN: If you can't outrun them,
- I don't know.
- Then you have one option.
Their motor cortex is partially exposed
at the back of their neck.
A knife to this area will disorient
their tracking device, but not for long.
Above all, stay alive. You have no idea
how important you are and how
important you will become.
The machines are advancing even faster
than I told you they would.
I've seen it with my own eyes.
They're inventing new Terminators,
new ways of killing us.
Skynet is planning something big.
But the Resistance is
planning something bigger.
This is John Connor.
If you're listening to this,
you are the Resistance.
John Connor.
We gotta find this guy.
[SPARKING]
MARCUS:
Ow.
- So you get it working?
- Almost.
Good. Look, I figure we head east, right?
We go through the desert, then we
can connect with the Resistance there.
- I'm heading north.
- No, no, no.
The machines control the whole
northern sector, up to San Francisco.
- That's Skynet Central.
- I have to find someone.
There's a lot that you don't
understand about Skynet, okay?
It's just too dangerous for us to go there.
What about the L.A. branch?
Come on, man. We need to get out of L.A.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[ALICE IN CHAINS' "ROOSTER" PLAYING
OVER CAR STEREO]
♪ Ain't found a way to kill me yet ♪♪
What is that?
Something my brother used to listen to.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Star, get out.
Don't look at me like that, Star.
Get out. Get out!
[SIGHS]
KYLE:
You're leaving? You're gonna leave us?
Oh, I get it.
You wanna know the difference
between us and the machines?
We bury our dead.
But no one is coming to bury you.
[WHIRRING]
KYLE:
Aerostat!
- It's a scout for the Terminators.
- Go, drive!
[♪♪♪]
The Aerostats heard the music!
[TYRES SQUEALING]
- Keep it steady!
- I've never driven before.
Hold the wheel!
[GRUNTING]
This thing's pissing me off!
Kid!
Hold on!
[TYRES SCREECHING]
[PANTING]
If the idea is to stay alive, I'm driving.
We're seeing a lot of
enemy movement in L.A.
Any of our people in the area?
No one on the ground.
Two A-10s in the air. Williams and Mihradi.
Send the birds in.
Guide them to a safe area.
MAN 1: Roger, Coyote 67 copies all.
Inbound to grid Lima-Alpha,
125793. Over.
- MAN 2: Copy that.
- BLAIR: Roger, Wild Eagle. Solid copy.
[GLASS CLINKS]
[CREAKING]
Hey, there's someone here.
[♪♪♪]
MAN 1:
Get off him, get down! Get down. Down!
- MAN 2: Drop your weapon!
- MAN 3: Let me see your hands!
- MAN 4: Don't move.
- MAN 5: That's it, drop it.
- MAN 6: Put it down!
- MAN 7: What?
Is there a problem?
KYLE:
Hey, we saw your Resistance sign.
LEN:
The old lady put it there, not me.
- What do you want?
- We're looking for fuel.
LEN:
The dark season's coming.
We only got enough for ourselves.
You point that gun at somebody,
you better be ready to pull the trigger.
Put your guns down, everyone.
Look, we just came to find the
Resistance, that's all.
The Resistance? Pfft.
What a joke.
Fighting those machines is impossible.
We keep our heads down, they ignore us.
You keep your heads down
and they'll come for you eventually.
We help you, maybe they will.
These people aren't gonna help you.
Let's go.
VIRGINIA:
You're not going anywhere.
Not until this one gets something to eat.
[BANGING ON FLOOR]
Bring me a basket.
Here you go.
Come on. Help yourself. Eat up.
Are you all right, son?
[SHOTGUN RACKS]
LEN:
It's our food.
Our fuel. It's not your choice to make!
[RUMBLING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[MARCUS SCREAMS]
- KYLE: Are you okay?
- What?
KYLE:
Are you okay?!
- KYLE: Star. Star.
- MARCUS: Star! Star!
You! You brought them here!
[GRUNTS]
MARCUS:
Hey!
- MAN 1: Stop! Stop!
- MARCUS: Come on, quick!
- MARCUS: Hey.
- MAN 2: Go! Go! Forget them! Go! Go!
MARCUS:
Go!
- MAN 3: Tunnels! Head for the tunnels!
- MARCUS: Truck!
[KYLE GRUNTS]
Marcus. Marcus.
We can't just run for it!
[ROBOT FOOTSTEPS THUDDING]
MAN 4:
Run!
[VIRGINIA SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[ROBOT FOOTSTEPS THUDDING]
[GRUNTING]
MARCUS:
Shoot it!
Go, go, go!
[GRUNTS]
It didn't work!
Shit!
[TRUCK ENGINE REVS]
KYLE:
Ha. Hell, yeah!
Oh.
[♪♪♪]
Moto-Terminators!
Shoot that son of a bitch!
[TYRES SQUEALING]
KYLE:
Marcus, turn right up here.
[TYRES SCREECHING]
Hold on!
KYLE:
Where's the other one?
[GRUNTING]
Get up here!
Ugh. Ah!
MARCUS:
Come on.
KYLE:
Star, give me the gun.
I got it.
Yeah!
Hang on!
- Drop the ball!
- KYLE: All right.
Ah!
[TYRES SQUEALING]
- KYLE: Star, hold on!
- MARCUS: Ah!
- KYLE: Star! Star!
- MARCUS: No!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[KYLE SCREAMS]
[MARCUS SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
- MARCUS: Kyle!
- KYLE: Marcus.
MARCUS:
Get back.
[MARCUS GRUNTING]
Marcus! Marcus!
Ah!
MAN [ON RADIO]:
Got eyes on two targets.
BLAIR [ON RADIO]:
We've got two bogeys at 270 degrees.
JOHN: They've never come this deep before.
They're looking for something.
BLAIR [ON RADIO]:
H.K. is down.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
MAN [ON RADIO]:
We've got an H.K. pushing our six.
- BLAIR [ON RADIO]: Abort run.
- MAN [ON RADIO]: Breaking off.
Evasive manoeuvres now!
BLAIR:
Taking fire. I'm hit. Port-side damage.
It's got a lock on you. Break off.
- Eject, Williams, eject!
- BLAIR: Punching out.
[GASPS]
Prisoner transport headed northwest,
bearing 289 toward San Francisco.
[♪♪♪]
Let's test the signal...
and pray it works.
Ah.
[BLAIR GRUNTS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Ugh.
MARCUS:
You okay?
Get my knife. It's in my left boot.
[BLAIR PANTING]
What's your name?
Blair Williams.
What's yours?
[GRUNTS]
Name's Marcus.
You can let me down now, Marcus.
[♪♪♪]
- That thing, where'd it go?
- The transport? Skynet.
- Where the hell are you going?
- After it.
I hate to break it to you,
but if you've got friends on that thing,
they're as good as dead.
And same as you,
if you keep walking in that direction.
Yeah, well, I've been dead a
while and I'm getting used to it.
Why don't you come with me to my base?
Connor might know a way.
Listen, if you got a
problem with the machines,
he's definitely the guy you wanna talk to.
- How far is your base?
- Should be one or two days' hike.
And it's that way.
[GUN COCKS]
[PEOPLE SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[SPEAKING IN CHINESE]
What are you saying? Speak English!
I was telling him it is not true
about the machines killing us.
They're gonna kill us.
They're gonna kill everyone.
We're in a cattle car,
on the way to the slaughterhouse!
Calm down. You're not helping.
The most important thing we
can do right now is stay alive.
In here and in here.
All right? Just stay alive.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Over there.
Find something we can burn.
We'll be at my base tomorrow.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
[THUNDER CRACKLES]
CARNAHAN:
What do you got there?
BLAIR:
Just some antibiotics.
TURNBULL:
Antibiotics are hard to come by these days.
Listen. I don't have much,
but you're welcome to whatever you need.
TURNBULL:
We've been watching you.
[CARNAHAN WHISTLES]
You looking for this?
Come on, guys. The machines are the enemy.
- We're all on the same side.
- CARNAHAN: No, no.
You see, I got a couple friends on my side.
Maybe they can carry you
home when I'm done with you.
[GUN COCKS]
You might want to chamber a round.
- RICHTER: Oh, no.
- BLAIR: No.
[GRUNTING]
RICHTER:
We done caught us a donkey!
CARNAHAN:
Been waiting for you.
[GRUNTING]
[BLAIR YELLS]
[SQUEALS]
[SHOTGUN RACKS]
[SHOTGUN FIRES]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
Killing me ain't gonna win this war.
Ah! Oh, God! Oh!
[CARNAHAN GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[BLAIR SIGHS]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[WHISPERS]
I'm a little cold.
Relax.
I just want some body heat.
[♪♪♪]
You have a strong heart.
God, I love that sound.
[EXHALES]
Thank you for saving me back there.
I don't meet a lot of good guys these days.
I'm not a good guy.
You are.
You just don't know it yet.
Do you think people
deserve a second chance?
Yeah, I do.
BARNES: This is it. Skynet's valley of
death. We never been this deep before.
JOHN: We gotta be sure the
signal works in their territory
on the bigger machines.
[ZIPPER ZIPS]
JOHN:
That'll bring them in.
H.K. incoming.
[BEEPING]
Turn it up!
[H.K. POWERS DOWN]
JOHN:
Oh...
[♪♪♪]
BARNES: It works, man.
The signal works. It's beautiful.
[PANTING]
BARNES:
Commander Ashdown's on.
ASHDOWN [ON RADIO]:
Connor, tell me it works.
It works. That is affirmative.
The signal works.
Good. The attack commences
tomorrow at 0400, worldwide.
Your unit will be in support of
the bombing of Skynet Central.
What is the extraction
plan for the prisoners?
Extraction plan?
There is no extraction plan.
- We're gonna level the place.
- Negative. I told you...
Skynet Central is filled
with human prisoners!
This is war, Connor.
Leadership has its costs.
You, above all, should know that.
Ashdown, come in!
Ashdown, Connor.
Ashdown, come... Damn him!
[CHATTERING AND SCREAMING]
[♪♪♪]
KYLE:
Star! Get back! Get back!
[GRUNTING]
You have to calm down now.
MAN:
I gotta get out! I gotta get out of here!
[GRUNTING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Blair?
What?
This is us. The mines are magnetic.
If we head due west at this
point of entry, we're good.
I'll go first.
Let's go, Marcus. I'm starving.
[YELLING]
PRIEST [IN VOICE-OVER]:
For thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff, they comfort me.
MARCUS:
Father.
SERENA:
This is the beginning
of something wonderful.
[CHOKING]
MORRISON:
Son of a bitch is heavy.
- What have we got here?
- He stepped on a land mine.
Start a large-bore IV.
- Keep it open. More morphine.
- I'm okay.
- What's his name?
- Marcus.
- He's got a prosthetic limb?
- What?
Okay, pulse is good.
Let's see what we've got here.
[GRUNTS]
Barnes.
JOHN:
The devil's hands have been busy.
What is it?
It's real flesh and blood,
though it seems to heal itself quickly.
The heart is human and very powerful.
The brain, too, but with a chip interface.
MARCUS:
What have you done to me?
It has a hybrid nervous system.
One human cortex, one machine.
MARCUS:
Blair, what have they done?
Who built you?
MARCUS:
My name is Marcus Wright.
You think you're human?
MARCUS:
I am human.
[♪♪♪]
[CHAIN CLINKS]
No!
JOHN:
Where were you manufactured?
I was born
August 22nd, 1975.
No.
[MARCUS SCREAMING]
MARCUS:
I know you.
I heard your voice on the radio.
- You're John Connor.
- JOHN: Of course you know me.
You were sent here to kill me.
Kill the leadership.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Then why are you here?
Blair said you could help
me find who I'm looking for.
- Now, let me down.
- If I let you down,
you'll kill everyone in this room.
Just you, Connor.
Because I don't give a shit about you.
I didn't even know your
name till two days ago.
No.
You and me,
we've been at war since before
either of us even existed.
You tried killing my mother, Sarah Connor.
You killed my father, Kyle Reese.
You will not kill me.
Kyle Reese is on a transporter
heading for Skynet.
If I wanted to kill him,
I would have done him in L.A.
JOHN:
Where'd you find that thing?
You sent Mihradi and me to
provide cover for some civilians.
- He was one of them.
- Was there a teenage boy?
I honestly don't know. They were taken
into a transport. He was the only one left.
Not "he," Blair. "It."
It was the only one left. Don't be naïve.
It saved my life.
Kate, what's gonna happen to him?
Disassembled.
- You mean, killed.
- It may have information on Skynet.
[SIGHS]
I know he's not the enemy. I've been
shot at by the enemy. That's not him.
That machine saved you only to
gain access to kill all of us.
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR SLAMS AND LOCKS]
We're gonna be okay. Don't worry.
[KYLE SCREAMING]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
For my brother.
[BULLET CLICKS]
[GUN SNAPS SHUT AND COCKS]
No!
[MARCUS PANTING]
Connor wants to see you.
What for?
Like he's gonna tell me, Barnes.
Let me see that.
[GUN COCKS]
BLAIR:
Want me to tell Connor you're not coming?
No.
BARNES:
Watch him.
[DOOR SQUEAKS AND SLAMS]
[MARCUS SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
SARAH [ON TAPE]:
I told you everything I know, John.
Skynet is ruthless and unpredictable.
They will use the best part
of you against yourself.
And they will have methods
I can't imagine or predict
that I can't help you with.
And when you're unsure,
well, just always follow your heart, John.
I love you. Goodbye.
[TAPE CLICKS OFF]
There's nothing in the tapes
about machines with organs.
That thing in there...
I thought I knew our enemy.
But that thing,
that makes me feel like I know nothing.
I looked in its eyes, and it believes,
absolutely believes
that it is human.
It believes everything that it says.
And it is telling me
that Kyle Reese is in Skynet.
If that is true,
then Command is about to bomb my father
and the rest of those prisoners
and I cannot stop them.
[BLAIR GRUNTING]
Thank you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Come in.
What's up? Blair said you needed me.
[ALARM RINGING]
[GAS HISSING]
MARCUS:
Get in.
[GUNS COCKING]
BARNES:
Get him.
[MARCUS SCREAMS]
Barnes! What about Blair?
She made her choice.
MARCUS:
Get down!
[PANTING]
MARCUS:
Let's move.
[BANGING]
[GRUNTS THEN PANTS]
- MAN 1: Get some light out there!
- MARCUS: We're back in the minefield.
BLAIR:
I have a plan.
[GRUNTS]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
MARCUS:
Let's run!
MAN 2:
There they go, they're on the move.
[BULLETS WHIZZING]
- MARCUS: Blair, you okay?
- BLAIR: Yeah, I'm okay!
- MAN 3: I can't see back!
- MAN 4: There they are!
MARCUS:
Run! Go!
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Now what?
My plan stopped at the jeep.
MAN 5:
Sniper Team 1, do you have a shot?
[GUNFIRE]
I'll draw the fire. You take out the light.
[PANTING]
MAN 1:
I got a target!
MARCUS: Go! Now! Keep your head down!
Keep your head down!
- Go, go, go!
- MAN 2: Go, go, go!
MARCUS:
Go! Go, keep running!
[BLAIR GRUNTS]
MARCUS:
Come on! Come on!
- You all right?
- Let's get you out of here.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
MAN 3:
There they are!
MAN 1:
Stay on the ground! Stay on the ground!
MAN 2 [ON RADIO]:
You come on straight down. I'm going in.
- MAN 3: Do not move!
- MAN 4: Keep your eye on him!
MAN 1:
Flip him!
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[MOTORCYCLE APPROACHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[GUNFIRE]
MAN [ON RADIO]: Iron Gator, this is
Scarface 51. We have eyes on the machine.
Contact initiated.
[GRUNTING]
Take my gun!
[DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE]
JOHN [OVER P.A.]:
Check the river.
You see him?
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM BEEPING]
JOHN:
Hydraulics are out!
[SCREAMING]
[PILOT YELLS]
JOHN:
Give me your hand! Give me your hand!
[♪♪♪]
[HYDROBOTS WHIRRING]
[MARCUS YELLS]
- They know what you are, even if you don't.
- Enough!
That gun ain't gonna stop shit!
Nobody's shot you in the heart, and I
see that thing beating a mile a minute!
Kyle Reese.
He's in Skynet. You do that, he's dead.
I can get you in.
How?
[♪♪♪]
Look at me.
That's why I don't trust you.
I'm the only hope you have.
I need to find who did this to me.
So do you.
SOLDIER:
Connor!
Make your choice.
You get me in.
You tell me where I can find Kyle Reese.
Yeah?
I will.
Contact me on that.
Let me know he's still alive.
What are you?!
I don't know.
SOLDIER:
Hey! He's over here!
[DOG BARKING]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
You all right?
Any sign of him?
He's gone.
[DOOR OPENS]
Why'd you do it?
I saw a man,
not a machine.
How's that leg?
- I'll live.
- Let her go!
COMMS OFFICER:
Connor? Command for you.
- This is Connor.
- Connor, are your men ready?
JOHN:
Negative. Nobody is ready.
We are not, you are not. We must
abort the attack. The game has changed.
What are you talking about? All our
elements are past their release points.
They are in assault position.
Then delay the attack.
At least, delay the attack.
I have a chance to infiltrate Skynet and rescue
those prisoners. Give me that opportunity.
No, absolutely not!
This is not the time for a rescue mission!
What you ask for will
undermine the whole operation.
Skynet has Kyle Reese.
- Then that is his fate.
- No. It's our fate.
I have to save him. He is the key.
The key to the future, to the past.
Without him, we lose everything.
No, you stay the course!
If we stay the course, we are dead!
We are all dead!
As of this moment, soldier,
you are relieved of your command.
You are no longer a
part of this Resistance.
I didn't catch that last statement.
Neither did I.
This is John Connor.
If you're listening to this,
you are the Resistance.
[OVER RADIO]
Listen carefully.
If we attack tonight,
our humanity is lost.
Command wants us to fight like machines.
They want us to make cold,
calculated decisions.
But we are not machines.
And if we behave like them,
then what is the point in winning?
Command is going to ask
you to attack Skynet.
I am asking you not to.
If even one bomb drops
on Skynet before sunrise,
our future will be lost.
So, please, stand down.
Give me the time
to protect our future that all of us
are fighting for.
This is John Connor.
[♪♪♪]
What should I tell your men
when they find out you're gone?
I'll be back.
[GUNS N' ROSES' "YOU COULD BE MINE" PLAYING
ON STEREO]
♪ Now holidays come and then they go ♪
♪ It's nothin' new today ♪
♪ Collect another memory ♪
♪ 'Cause you could be mine ♪♪
[♪♪♪]
I'm coming for you.
Come on, Marcus.
[♪♪♪]
Kyle.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
Signal broadcasting at full strength, sir.
Good. Commence bombing of Skynet.
SOLDIER:
We have a green light for the attack.
RESISTANCE MEMBER 1: This is Bakersfield.
That's a no-go on your last. Out.
RESISTANCE MEMBER 2:
Eugene, standing down.
RESISTANCE MEMBER 3:
This is Reno. Negative.
SOLDIER: Eugene, Reno, Bakersfield.
They're all standing down.
They will not attack unless
Connor gives the order.
[♪♪♪]
[POWERS DOWN]
[PEOPLE YELLING]
[YELLS]
Kyle Reese?
Get to the transport! Go!
Is Kyle Reese here?!
Welcome home, Marcus.
We knew you'd be back.
After all, it was programmed in you.
Oh. And you executed that
programming beautifully.
What am I?
You are an infiltration prototype.
The only one of your kind.
We resurrected you,
advanced Cyberdyne's work, amended it.
You're dead.
Calculations confirm Serena Kogan's face...
Is the easiest for you to process.
We can be others if you wish.
Marcus, what else could you be...
- [IN KYLE'S VOICE]
- -if not machine?
A man.
[IN SERENA'S VOICE] The human
condition no longer applies to you.
Accept what you already know.
That you were made to serve a purpose.
To achieve what no other
machine has achieved before.
To infiltrate, find a target,
and then bring that target back home to us.
We've been at war since before
either of us even existed.
You tried killing my mother, Sarah Connor.
You get me in.
You tell me where I can find Kyle Reese.
- Yeah?
- MARCUS [ON SPEAKER]: I will.
[ALL YELLING]
JOHN:
Kyle Reese! Kyle Reese! Move! Move!
Kyle Reese!
Get to the transports!
- Kyle Reese?
- No.
[YELLS]
JOHN:
You! Move!
In times of desperation, people
will believe what they want to believe.
And so, we gave them what
they wanted to believe.
A trick, in the form of a signal
the Resistance thought would win the war.
And they were right, it will end this war.
Except that it is the Resistance
that will be terminated.
Not Skynet.
[♪♪♪]
ASHDOWN: Get the attack of
Skynet Central back online.
I want our aircraft in the sky immediately.
Sir. Sir, we've got a bogey with
a very large radar signature
closing in on our position.
Losenko?
We have destroyed ourselves.
Skynet tracked our signal.
We led them straight to us.
[SCREAMING]
Our best machines had failed time and again
to complete a mission.
Something was missing.
We had to think. Radically.
And so we made you. We created
the perfect infiltration machine.
You, Marcus.
You did what Skynet has failed
to do for so many years.
You killed John Connor.
[DEVICE BEEPING]
[BEEPING RAPIDLY]
[JOHN GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
Kyle!
Hey!
Don't fight, Marcus.
Remember what you are.
I know what I am.
[GRUNTS]
I'm better this way.
You will not be given a second chance.
- You cannot save John Connor.
- Watch me.
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[ALARM WAILING]
Got a message from Connor.
He's in Skynet, needs air support.
Let's go. Scramble aircraft!
[CHEERING]
[GROANS]
Star! Star, go!
Star!
Star! Star! Come on. Come on.
Run! Run!
- What's your name?
- Kyle Reese.
[♪♪♪]
[GUNFIRE]
JOHN:
Stay with me.
[GRUNTS]
Back!
KYLE:
Come on, Star, move! Move!
[GRUNTING]
JOHN:
T-800s.
KYLE:
There's so many of them.
JOHN:
Careful.
- What are these?
- JOHN: Fuel cells.
Life source for the T-800.
Nuclear.
Enough to level this place.
Cover us.
[ELEVATOR BEEPS]
Get ready.
This is it.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
JOHN:
Run!
Star, come on! Let's go!
Get in.
Come on!
We gotta get to the transport.
- KYLE: Where are you going?
- I gotta end this.
No, no. I'm not gonna leave you!
- You didn't.
- Who are you?
John Connor.
[♪♪♪]
[JOHN GROANING]
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪]
[MARCUS GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
KYLE: Hey! Hey, John Connor's in there.
He's still in there.
Chris, she's hypovolemic, start a line!
- What?
- John Connor's in there.
Come with me.
[KYLE'S VOICE]
Connor!
Connor, help!
Help!
Connor, it's Kyle. Help!
[GRUNTS AND GROANS]
Do it! You son of a bitch!
[YELLS]
Come on!
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
[GASPING]
MARCUS:
Let's get out of here.
John.
[♪♪♪]
BARNES: We can't make it back to base.
Set this down in the nearest safe zone.
BLAIR [ON RADIO]:
Medevac, urgent. Severe chest trauma.
Call the surgical team.
Remarks: It's Connor.
[EKG MONITOR BEEPING]
How long?
His heart...
can't take it.
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be okay, Kate.
JOHN:
Kyle?
[♪♪♪]
Take it.
You earned it.
Kate?
Take mine.
BLAIR:
Marcus...
Everybody deserves a second chance.
This is mine.
[EXHALES]
[♪♪♪]
MARCUS:
What is it that makes us human?
It's not something you can programme.
You can't put it into a chip.
It's the strength of the human heart.
The difference between us and machines.
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
JOHN:
There is a storm on the horizon.
A time of hardship and pain.
This battle has been won,
but the war against the machines rages on.
Skynet's global network remains strong.
But we will not quit
until all of it is destroyed.
This is John Connor.
There is no fate but what we make.
[♪♪♪]